https://www.promax.com/privacy-statement

Who We Do It For
Who Loves ProMAX?
Is ProMAX Right for you?
Customer Success Stories
Why ProMAX?
Who We Do It For
Who Loves ProMAX?
Is ProMAX Right for you?
Customer Success Stories
Why ProMAX?
Who We Do It For
Who Loves ProMAX?
Is ProMAX Right for you?
Customer Success Stories
Why ProMAX?
Privacy Statement
ProMAX Systems is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the ProMAX Systems Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the ProMAX Systems website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
ProMAX Systems collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. ProMAX Systems also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by ProMAX Systems. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by ProMAX Systems for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the ProMAX Systems Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through ProMAX Systems public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: ProMAX Systems does not read any of your private online communications.
ProMAX Systems encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from ProMAX Systems so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. ProMAX Systems is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the ProMAX Systems and ProMAX Systems family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
ProMAX Systems collects and uses your personal information to operate the ProMAX Systems Web site and deliver the services you have requested. ProMAX Systems also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from ProMAX Systems and its affiliates. ProMAX Systems may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
ProMAX Systems does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. ProMAX Systems may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, ProMAX Systems may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to ProMAX Systems, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
ProMAX Systems does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
ProMAX Systems keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within ProMAX Systems, in order to determine what ProMAX Systems services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within ProMAX Systems to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
ProMAX Systems Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on ProMAX Systems or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of ProMAX Systems; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of ProMAX Systems, or the public.
You may easily opt out of our email list here: unsubscribe
GDPR and European Policies
As of May 25th, 2018; ProMAX Systems will maintain compliance with GDPR laws and regulations.  For European contacts in our database that have not purchased ProMAX Products and are not ProMAX channel partners, information will be removed and deleted from our database, unless you have visited this page to explicitly opt in to our email marketing.
For European contacts that are ProMAX customers or channel partners, your information will maintain in our database as outlined in the privacy policy, as this information is critical to deliver product, support and policy information and updates for your business.  If you are a ProMAX customer or channel partner and wish not to receive this information you may easily opt out of our email list here:
European customers will be deleted from our database 6 years after the last point of purchase.
Use of Cookies
The ProMAX Systems Web site uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize ProMAX Systems pages, or register with ProMAX Systems site or services, a cookie helps ProMAX Systems to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same ProMAX Systems Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the ProMAX Systems features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the ProMAX Systems services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
ProMAX Systems secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. ProMAX Systems secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
ProMAX Systems will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. ProMAX Systems encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how ProMAX Systems is protecting your information.
Contact Information
ProMAX Systems welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that ProMAX Systems has not adhered to this Statement, please contact ProMAX Systems at Jess.Hartmann@promax.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
ProMAX Systems
2850 S. Fairview St. Santa Ana, CA,  92704
Phone: (949)-346-1231
About ProMAX
News & Events
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
Copyright © 2018 Company, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
